[
    {
        "front": "きます ❘❘\n[シャツを]",
        "back": "put on (shirt, jacket etc.)",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "はきます ❘❘\n[くつを]",
        "back": "put on (shoes, trousers etc.)",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "かぶります ❘❘\n[ぼうしを]",
        "back": "put on (a hat etc)",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "かけます ❘❘\n[めがねを]",
        "back": "put on (glasses)",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "うまれます ❘❘",
        "back": "be born",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "コート",
        "back": "Coat",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "スーツ",
        "back": "Suit",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "セーター",
        "back": "Sweater",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぼうし",
        "back": "Hat, Cap",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "めがね",
        "back": "Glasses",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "よく",
        "back": "often",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "おめでとうございます",
        "back": "congratulations (used on birthdays, weddings etc)",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "こちら",
        "back": "this (polite equivalent of これ)",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "やちん",
        "back": "house rent",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "うーん",
        "back": "hmmm (Let me see)",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "ダイニングキッチン",
        "back": "Kitchen with Dining area",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "わしつ",
        "back": "Japanese style room",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "おしいれ",
        "back": "Japanese style almirah",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふとん",
        "back": "Japanese style mattress and quilt",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "アパート",
        "back": "Apartment",
        "chapter": "N5 C22"
    }
]